twimailer.com 2014-06-22

# Cherrp - Privacy Policy

As the owners ("Company" or "we") of Cherrp (the "Web Site"), we have created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of our customers and users. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Web Site, and not any other websites that are accessible from the Web Site, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such web sites. 

In order for you to access certain services that we offer via the Web Site, we require you to provide us with certain information that personally identifies you which includes: contact information such as your name, mailing address, telephone number, facsimile number and e-mail address and financial data such as your credit card number and social security number and/or tax identification number. We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information from you when you visit the Web Site such as your: IP address; web request; domain server; type of web browser you used to access the Web Site; and your approximate geographic location. 

We use your contact information that you provide to contact you when necessary. We use the financial data that you provide to verify your qualifications for certain services and to bill you for services. We do not rent, sell or share any personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide the services you've requested.

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to enable us to personalize your experience with our Web Site. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze our Web Site usage and/or provide this information to third parties for the same purpose, as well as to offer you products or services.

On occasion we may share your non-personally identifiable information that we collect and personal information that you provide to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Company's Terms and Conditions, in order to diagnose a problem with our server, to administer our Web Site or as we otherwise deem necessary in our sole and absolute discretion. We will transfer information about you if the Company is acquired by or merged with another company and this may occur with or without notice to you. Also, we will provide your personal information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

We provide our customers with unique usernames and passwords for use with our services. We use this information for security purposes and to prevent unauthorized use, access, alteration or misuse of your accounts and services.

We have reasonable security measures in place and technologies to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of your information under our control but we cannot assure that your personally identifiable information or non-personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

To Change and/or Modify Information We allow our customers to change and modify personal information previously provided by either using their account manager.

To enhance the performance of certain services within our Web Site we use cookies. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your personally identifiable information. However, once you choose to furnish the Web Site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the offerings on our Web Site. Cookies placed on your computer by third parties by or through the Web Site, if any, are not the responsibility of the Company and are not subject to this Privacy Policy. Please contact the third party placing these cookies to find out what information is collected and how it is used. You can usually edit your browser not to accept cookies, but the features of our Web Site may not function properly if you do accept cookies.
